Welcome to the show!
Today we're testing batch translation.
This file has exactly 30 cues.
Testing context windows...
Bold text should be preserved.
Regular subtitle line here.
Top-aligned text
Italic text for emphasis
Normal line again.
This is cue number ten.
Second batch should start around here.
If batch size is 25, we're in batch 1.
Testing overflow behavior.
Red text
Halfway through!
More content...
Line seventeen.
Line eighteen.
Line nineteen.
Twenty!
Getting close to the end.
Line twenty-two.
Line twenty-three.
Line twenty-four.
Exactly at batch boundary!
Second batch if size=25.
Line twenty-seven.
Almost done...
Penultimate cue.
The end! Goodbye!